Sara Torkamani



Customer Service Specialist

Dedicated and trustworthy customer service specialist with 7+ years of experience in online software troubleshooting, tech support, and customer care. Strong communication skills, organized, with a track record of success. Talented in simplifying complex problems, making it easy for non-technical specialists to solve IT issues.

🔀 sara.torkamani@live.com



v3.0.0

Professional Experience

Co-Founder, Customer Service Specialist

Jibres

(2 years 4 months) 12/2019 - present

- Resolved customer complaints quickly and efficiently, resulting in a 20% increase in customer satisfaction ratings and over 10% decrease in return rates.
- Resolved an average of 50+ customer inquiries per day via email, phone, and live chat, maintaining a customer satisfaction rating of 80% or higher.
- Improved customer self-service by creating and implementing a comprehensive knowledge base, resulting in a 50% decrease in support requests.

Founder and Manager

Bitty Style

(1 year 8 months) 07/2020 - 02/2022

- Established an online clothing store and increased sales revenue by 150% by utilizing strategic marketing campaigns, social media engagement, and customer satisfaction programs.
- Created relationships with multiple suppliers, resulting in a diverse product line and 25% higher profit margins.
- Analyzed customer buying patterns and optimized product offerings resulting in a 20% increase in sales revenue within the first quarter of management.

Office Manager

Ermile

(4 years 7 months) 06/2015 - 12/2019

- Enhanced employee productivity and reduced overhead costs by 30% through implementated and maintenanced of effective office
 management systems, by reducing paper use, the organization also achieved a more eco-friendly workplace.
- Improved office productivity by renegotiating vendor contracts and finding cost-effective solutions and managed the office relocation project, ensuring a seamless transition and minimizing disruptions.

Sales Associate

Noshahr.com

(2 years 3 months) 02/2013 - 04/2015

 Achieved over 40% revenue growth by exceeding sales targets through effective communication and building strong customer relationship.

Education

M.S. in Business Administration - MBA, Strategy

Azad University (Unfinished)

2022 - 2022

B.S. in English Translation

TMQU - Toloue Mehr Qom Higher Education Institute

2016 - 2021

B.S. in Food Science and Technology

Khazar Institute of Higher Education

2012 - 2014

A.S. in Chemical Industry

TVU - Technical and Vocational University

2010 - 2012

Skills

Persistence

Collaboration

Presentation

Word

Excel Po

PowerPoint

Teamwork

Scrum

Languages

English Fluent B2 Persian Native

Azerbaijani Native